Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
How's the shoot going?
I can't tell if I'm brilliant.
or if I'll never work again.
How have you been. Frank?
I've missed you terribly...
Mr. Sinatra. I'm so
sorry to bother you.
No bother at all.
Would you mind
signing my napkin?
Wow. I... I could die happy now.
Now. don't do that.
Oh. and my wife loved you in
Peyton Place. Miss Farrow.
Thank you. That's...
You remember what I told you?
I just don't think it's fair.
Marriage isn't
about what's fair.
You can't ask me to choose
between you and
this movie. Frank.
It's not just the movie. baby.
It's a lifestyle.
If we're both always out on the
road... I know. but this is my career.
Don't... Don't interrupt me.
I'm getting the check.
If you go back to
that set today. Mia
we're through.
We're a third of the way
through filming. Frank.
And Bob's sure I'll get
an Oscar nomination.
How do you expect
to be a good mother
if this is what you're chasing?
I'll figure it out.
Women always do.
Good luck with that. kid.
How you doing - in there?
- Fine.
Thank you.
- Mia. new idea.
- Mmm.
So. you walk into the
street. distracted. scared...
The street... And
there'll be picture cars?
Picture cars? No.
You don't mean...
You want me stepping into
actual traffic. Roman?
Don't worry. Mia.
No one's going to
hit a pregnant woman.
Roman's a pussycat
underneath all the bluster.
Mmm. Thanks. Sharon.
The devil is
beautiful. you know?
And you'd find him in the
people you'd never expect.
All set. Mia?
Just right over here.
Rolling!
And action!
Mia?
- I'm coming.
I can help you if you let me.
What do you mean?
Take it off.
How did you know?
Women's intuition.
My mother wasn't
always easy to love.
and she often wasn't the
mother I thought I needed.
But in the days since her
passing. I've realized...
I don't know what I need.
I don't know if any of us do.
She was
the mother I was given.
And
she was perfect.
As many of you know.
in lieu of flowers.
we've asked loved ones to donate
to the American Foundation
for Suicide Prevention.
Your mother did
not kill herself.
She was killed.
Respectfully. ma'am. I
have to ask you to leave.
You! You did not listen to her!
She tried to warn you
over and over and over!
Her blood is on your hands!
Don't fucking touch me!
Don't... No. Don't
you fucking touch me!
Do you see?
This is what happens to
women who tell the truth!
I beg you. listen to your wife!
Listen to your wife!
Please. Please. I beg
you. listen to your wife!
I'm very sorry about that.
I don't know who that woman is.
Um.
Father Matthews.
I have to say. I'm not gonna
miss the alimony payments.
Let us go in peace
to live out the word of God.
Thank you for coming.
Have a blessed day.
Anna. you're as big as a house.
You sure you don't
have twins in there?
Excuse me? Can you tell
me where that woman went?
Crazy one?
Sent her to the ER.
Why?
To be sedated.
You her daughter?
No.
Oh. just assumed.
She's heavily sedated.
Won't be herself.
I'll give you a minute.
I'm sorry I didn't believe you.
They will...
They will take
everything from you.
All of your dreams will
become a nightmare.
Please. get out now.
Look who woke up for her
guest. Ah. poor babe.
- No.
- Here.
We just want her
to be comfortable.
No.
- It's okay. You're okay.
Where did she go?[nurse 2] Hmm?
Oh. some friends
came to pick her up.
What friends?
Some women. They seemed nice.
Oh. my God.
Congratulations!
This is crazy.
We got an Oscar nominee in here!
You're here and you're here.
Never happened to me before.
I've never been this close
to somebody who's famous.
Who are you gonna bring?
Are you sure you're
up for flying?
Yes. I'm only seven
months pregnant.
I mean. even though I'm
practically spherical.
That's my girl.
Besides. nothing went wrong
last time I flew to LA.
Dr. Hill's probably
just covering his ass
so he doesn't get
sued or something.
As long as you know
it's your call.
These would look
amazing with the Gucci.
but we might want
something simpler.
Yes. I think I love the Gucci.
- Is that your phone?
- No. Is it yours?
Obviously not.
Why does Dex have a
fucking flip phone?
He doesn't.
Who's calling him?
It says. "Unknown caller."
Oh. my God.
This is where Harvey Weinstein
ejaculated into a plant.
- Stop.
- Iconic.
Wait. You're going to
that gifting suite. right?
I don't... I don't
need any free shit.
It's not about the free shit.
It's about being seen.
You're making an appearance
and getting your photo taken
with every Keurig maker.
acid-washed pair of Levi's
and certificate for a HydraFacial
we can get our hands on.
- Hmm.
- Okay?
Hey.
- Anna. over here.
- Oh.
- Right this way.
- Congratulations. Ms. Alcott.
We'd love to offer you
our five-karat gold
morning glory misting spray.
Thank you. Oh.
- How does that feel?
- Anna. over here.
- Anna. just one over here.
- Right here. please.
- Anna!
- Beautiful! One more?
Can I get you this way?
Okay. Right this
way now. Anna. Oh.
Don't forget your misting spray.
Hello. Ms. Alcott.
May I offer you our
beta wave. cruelty-free.
silk sleep mask?
Would you. uh.
like to try it on?
Here you go.
It blocks out 99.9% of light.
so you will get your
smoothest sleep possible
before the big night.
Thank you.
Can you give me a minute?
Hi. Anna. Congratulations.
What are you doing here?
Manning my booth. silly.
Dr. Hill has a ton of
West Coast clientele.
and he wants to make
a dent at the Oscars
to expand our brand.
I'll be rooting for you Sunday.
I can explain.
Make yourselves at home.
If you change into your gown.
Dr. Hill will be in shortly.
Okay.
Thank you.
It all began in
such a simple way.
Such a cliché.
Oh. my God. You're amazing.
Open.
What is this?
It's yours.
You deserve this.
And it gets better.
I've set up cameras
so we can be together
even when we're not.
I'll wink at you
to say good night.
You're the best man
I've ever known.
I'm a piece of shit.
So am I.
We couldn't help ourselves.
But I became addicted
to watching you.
Your life just
seemed so perfect.
And I wanted it for myself.
I looked for ways
to take it all away.
You were supposed to be at
the clinic 20 minutes ago.
The egg retrieval's at 9:00 a.m.
Dr. Hill says he needs you
here as soon as possible
or we have to start this
whole cycle over again.
How fast can you get here?
Come right with me. Ms. Alcott.
Then you were there.
So close.
I felt our connection.
And in the end.
it all fell apart.
We need to talk.
I couldn't let you be happy.
Baby.
You're a fucking psychopath.
I never wanted you to
know. I really like you.
I wish I were you.
Is that what you're
doing here. huh?
You're stalking me?
No. I wanted to warn you
before it's too late.
Before what's too late?
They're doing
something to your baby.
Wait. Were you the one
leaving the dolls too?
What dolls?
Don't fucking lie to me. Cora.
It's them. Anna. It's all them.
- Who?
- The women Dr. Hill works with.
- What. you mean his patients?
- They pretend to be.
And they help him find new ones.
and they do terrible
things to them.
They're doing it
to you right now.
- Doing what?
- I don't know.
But I do know Dr. Hill
became the primary
fertility specialist
in New York City by
making sacrifices.
So why do you work for him?
I have student loans.
What happens to the babies?
I never see them delivered.
I just know Dr. Hill
administers different
medications to certain mothers.
He doesn't let them see
any outside specialists.
and he spends a lot
of time on the phone
before and after
their appointments
with the door closed.
And when he comes out. he's
like a different person.
Yeah. I know.
I'm not having this
conversation right now.
No. it's gonna be okay.
I know it's not gonna be...
Hey. babe.
You're back so early.
Whoa.
I'm just talking to Talia.
Get out.
Housekeeping.
No. thank you!
I said. "no. thank you."
Don't yell at me.
It's the big day. Half-caf?
- Bathroom emergency.
- Sorry.
Are you okay?
Are you shitting?
Yes.
Okay. Well. squeeze
that fucker out ASAP.
It's go time. bitch.
Plop. plop. Let's go.
Why are you covered in a sheet?
Did you sheet
yourself or something?
I'm sorry. that was a good one.
- Oh. my God.
- Don't.
You just cut yourself shaving.
You had me worried.
Oh. that's the glam squad.
I always knew he
was a piece of shit.
Never trust a man with
blonde highlights.
- Siobhan.
- What?
Like we're not gonna talk
about what a giant slimy turd
your husband is
for cheating on you
with a literal zygote.
You're seven-and-a-half
months pregnant.
Look. I just don't wanna
focus on that right now. okay?
This is my night.
You're right. Fuck yeah. it is.
And you know what?
You've worked so hard.
Not as hard as
I've asked you to.
but that's okay.
Everyone disappoints me.
You've worked so hard. and
you followed my direction.
I know it's gonna be worth it.
I promise.
You'd never. like.
lie to me. right?
About what. babe?
I don't know. People talk.
Let me guess.
That old bitch. Ms. Preecher?
She's been stalking
my socials lately too.
She's just lonely
and obsessed with us.
I mean. there's
two kinds of women:
Those who know it's
their responsibility
to lift others up.
and those who hate the ones
they'll never get to be.
What about Babette?
What about her?
I mean. you asked me
if I wanted an Oscar
as much as I wanted a baby.
and then the next day...
Oh. my God.
You think I. like. killed her?
Okay.
Enough feminist psychological
thrillers for you.
I mean. from now on.
it's exclusively rom-come
and brand ambassadorships.
Congratulations. Anna.
May the best nominee win.
- Anna! Anna! Anna!
- Are you okay?
Should we go to
the hospital? What?
Should we go to the hospital?
No. it's the Oscars.
Okay. Come on.
Okay. Are you sure?
My body would tell me
if something was wrong.
Okay.
Ladies and gentlemen.
welcome to the 96th
Annual Academy Awards.
What's wrong?
I think I just
had a contraction.
Okay. Just hold
tight. Good evening.
I want to take the
time to congratulate
all the incredible nominees
that are here tonight.
Yes.
I can't go into labor.
I'm only 30 weeks.
Some of whom are not even white.
Apparently. you can.
The Oscars have come a long way
the last few years.
We've let women host.
Okay. Just hold on till
we get to your category.
and then we'll go
to the hospital.
You are so strong.
Collectively. realized that
alopecia is never funny enough
to justify assault.
This year's
selection of nominees
in the Best Actress category
feature some of the
bravest performances
I have ever had the
honor to witness
in my career.
And the nominees are:
Anna Victoria
Alcott. The Auteur.
Donna Brooks. Silent Echo.
Do you want this?
Say yes.[presenter]
Babette Eno...
Yes.
What would you give up for it?
Ines Mariano...
Anything.
Anything?
And the Oscar goes to...
Congratulations.
Anna Victoria Alcott.
The Auteur.
Go get that hardware. baby.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Mom?
I... I...
We have to go. Siobhan.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org